Benjamin Thomas

Tampa, FL - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Benjamin-Thomas/ebb4fb0a3467ea7a

For the last few months I've had the time to work for myself as a Unity3D VR Game Developer but would like to return to the workforce as soon as possible. Most recently I've served as an I.T. Assistant Manager and Computer Programmer Analyst for The Salvation Army Florida Divisional Headquarters. I helped manage IT and also managed application development. I worked directly with our clients to ensure their software development and computer support needs were met. My secure, data-driven .Net ASP web applications are coded in C# or vb.net and employ encrypted SQL back-ends and SQL reporting services. I also provide high-level technical support for various software and hardware configurations. While performing a host of varied I.T technical duties, my goal has always been to provide exceptional service that goes beyond expectation.

- * Excellent at repairing computer problems, servers, and network issues
- * Excellent verbal and written communication
- * Excellent at managing application development and administration throughout the entire application lifecycle
- * Excellent with database management and development
- * Excellent trainer and sharer of information

Certifications: A+, Server +, IBM Lotus Notes Developer, MS Access AS Degree - Computer Programming from St. Petersburg College Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Unity3D Game Developer/Programmer

Nest Egg Games LLC - Tampa, FL - February 2017 to Present

Assistant IT Manager

The Salvation Army Florida Headquarters - Lutz, FL - March 2016 to February 2017

Computer Programmer Analyst

The Salvation Army Florida Headquarters - Lutz, FL - March 2013 to March 2016

Database Administrator

The Salvation Army Florida Headquarters - Lutz, FL - March 2008 to March 2013

Help Desk Specialist

The Salvation Army Florida Headquarters - Lutz, FL - September 2005 to March 2008

Receiving Clerk

First Hawaiian Bank - Honolulu, HI - 2002 to 2005

Assistant Manager

Pearl City, HI - 1999 to 2002

EDUCATION

A.S. in Windows Programming

St. Petersburg College 2006